http://www.icc107.com/privacy

ICC107.com
A reputation of excellence in the field of quality electronic components.
Theme Options
Background Image:
Privacy Policy
Protecting personal information is a core International Component Corporation values. This privacy statement describes how International Component Corporation collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding International Component Corporation's use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or delete it. If you submit personal information, such as your email address, to us by following the "Contact Us, Partner Information Request or Request a Quote" links located throughout our site, we will use that information to respond to your question or request for information. We will not share your information with third parties without your explicit permission.You can also contact us by email at info@icc107.com, call us at 800-645-9154 or by writing us at the following address:International Component Corporation215 McCormick Dr. Bohemia New York, 11716 Phone: 800-645-9154 Our servers automatically collect certain non-personally identifying information, such as your computer's IP address, the type of browser in use, and pages viewed, when you visit our site. We use this information to understand how visitors navigate through our site, to enhance your experience while using our site, and to make the materials we post as valuable to visitors as possible. We do not link this information to personally identifiable information. We will share your personal information with third parties in the ways that are described above in this privacy statement. We will also share your personal information if we are required to do so by law, or if we believe that doing so is necessary in order to conform to the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, comply with legal process served on International Component Corporation, or otherwise protect International Component Corporation's legal rights. From time to time we employ service providers to perform various functions involving personal information on our behalf. These service providers are prohibited from using this personal information for any other purpose.Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of International Component Corporation. If you submit personal information to any of those site, your information is subject to their privacy statements. International Component Corporation's privacy statement does not apply to information you may submit to those site. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect the personally identifying information we have collected through our site, we will post those changes in this space and advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes.
QUICK REQUEST FORM
* Required
Name *
Company *
Phone *
Email *
Choose
Request Sample
Contact Us
215 McCormick Dr.
Bohemia, New York 11716
Telephone (631) 952 - 9595
Fax: ( 631) 952 - 9597
Email oemsales@icc107.com
Copyright © 2020 International Components Corporation | All rights reserved | Designed & Maintained By Promptweb.com |
Privacy Policy
The information documented within this page is believed to be correct, but no guarantee or warranty, express or implied, with respect to accuracy, completeness or results is extended and no liability is assumed.
International Components Corporation reserves the right to make changes in any specification, data or material contained herein
